Regina Foster – Serious

kuttin4u@yahoo.com 816.469.6190

SUMMARY

Analytical mind with proficient technical skills in MS Excel, MS Word, MS PowerPoint and data management systems. Intermediate technical skills with SQL, HTML, CSS, and D3. Over 15 years experience in business analysis, performance reporting, customer service and project planning. Operational efficiency achieved through time management, humble communication and variance analysis along with ensuring data quality of research for informed resource allocation and forecasting. My career objective is to be an instrument for company growth that brings integrity-based work performance. reliable intelligence and effective information analysis.

WORK EXPERIENCE

EXL Service Real-Time Analyst September 2018 to November 2019 Lee's Summit, MO

Call Center - responsible for real-time and/or intraday management of resources to ensure the correct number of agents at the right times are in their seats to answer an accurately forecasted volume of incoming calls at the desired service level. MS Excel (VLookup/ Pivot Tables/Chart Analysis/Formulas) used daily for data analysis and streamlined performance reporting.

Kuttin Ground Spirit, LLC (M/WBE) Strategic Planner

May 2005 to October 2017 **USA** and Belize

Conducted program monitoring and evaluations (M&E) for small business incubation clients and non-profit community development grants. Achievements - \$7k, \$25k and \$100k grant awards.

Defined business requirements and reported planning strategies to executive decision makers. Achievements – 30 SBE launched 2008 thru 2014.

Performed SWAT analysis for developing operational, logistical and marketing plans. Achievements - Composed operational management plans, business models and capacity building training manuals for non-profit and for-profit small and medium sized businesses – 4 of 30 business plans received capital investments within 6 months of fund development. Analysed small business ERP systems and developed digital databases with reporting platforms for CRM, SCM, and BI using MS Excel (VLookup/ Pivot Tables/Chart Analysis/Formulas), MS Word (Mail Merge), MS Access (Relational database links), and MS Outlook email alerts.

Client industries included: Merchandising, Entertainment, Restaurants, Agriculture, Food Processing, Warehousing, Manufacturing, Tourism, Grassroots Organizations, and International Supply Chain Management.

Full Employment Council Administrative Assistant III

October 2003 to May 2005 Kansas City, MO

Produced and distributed correspondence to executive decision makers

Assisted in the preparation of regularly scheduled reports using MS Excel, Access, Word, and Powerpoint Handled multiple projects to support the CFO and COO with validation research, national workforce policy updates and experiential program innovation opportunities

EDUCATION

High School Diploma (3.8 G.P.A.) Van Horn Engineering and Technology

May 1992 Independence, MO

Global Supply Chain Management - Diploma Fundamental Design of Systems Design and Implementation - Certificate Alison Courses

December 2019 November 2019 Online